Guide to the E. S. Reddy Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Subject files
  - Statements and Resolutions Adopted at Conferences of Afro-Asian Peoples, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 380)
  - Steve Biko Case, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 381)
  - Student and Youth Action, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 382)
  - Sullivan Principles, undated (Box 7, Folder 383)
  - Sun City, 1982-1987 (Box 7, Folder 384)
  - Suzman, Helen, 1982-1989 (Box 7, Folder 385)
  - Swaziland, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 386)
  - Sweden, 1976-1986 (Box 7, Folder 387)
  - Tambo, Oliver, correspondence, 1963-1985 (Box 7, Folder 388)
  - Tambo, Oliver, speeches, 1963-1985 (Box 8, Folder 389 - 390)
  - Tanzania, 1965-1977 (Box 8, Folder 391)
  - Thatcher, Margaret, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 392)
  - Togo, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 393)
  - Trade Unions, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 394)
  - Transkei, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 395)
  - Transnational Corporations, 1978-1985 (Box 8, Folder 396)
  - Tutu, Desmond, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 397)
  - United Church Board for World Ministries (New York), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 398)
  - United Church of Christ, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 399)
  - United Methodist Church, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 400)
  - United Mine Workers of America, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 401)
  - UN Policy on Cultural Links, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 402)
  - United States Catholic Conference, 1976 July 7
  - United States of America, 1960-1990 (Box 8, Folder 403 - 404)
  - United States: South Africa Leader Exchange Program (USSALEP), 1980 (Box 8, Folder 405)
  - ComitéAnti-Apartheid Committee (Quebec), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 406)
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 407)
  - University of Cape Town, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 408)
  - University of Denver, undated (Box 8, Folder 409)
  - University of Dublin, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 410)
  - University of Durban: Westville, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 411)
  - University of Florida, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 412)
  - University of Illinois, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 413)
  - University of Maryland, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 414)
  - University of Natal, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 415)
  - University of Witwatersrand, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 416)
  - University of Western Cape, 1981-1991 (Box 8, Folder 417)
  - University of Zambia, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 418)
  - University of Zimbabwe, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 419)
  - Venketrathnam, Surinarayan, 1969-1978 (Box 8, Folder 420)
  - Verkyul, Johannes, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 421)
  - "Vrye Weekblad", 1989 (Box 8, Folder 422)
  - War on Want Campaign Against World Poverty (London), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 423)
  - Washington Observer, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 424)
  - Weinberg, Eli, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 425)
  - Western Action Against Apartheid (Papers), 1985 (Box 8, Folder 426)
  - Wisconsin, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 427)
  - World Bank, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 428)
  - World Confederation of Labour (Belgium), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 429)
  - World Council of Churches, 1976-1991 (Box 8, Folder 430)
  - World Federation of Democratic Youth (Budapest), 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 431)
  - World Liberation on Youth (Belgium), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 432)
  - World Peace Council, 1975-1989 (Box 8, Folder 433)
  - World Union of Karatedo Organization (WUKO), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 434)
  - World University Service (WUS), 1970-1984 (Box 8, Folder 435)
  - "World Watch", undated (Box 8, Folder 436)
  - Xundu, Mcebisi Osman, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 437)
  - Young, Thomas, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 438)
  - Youth Forum of the European Communities (Brussels), 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 439)
  - Zaire, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 440)
  - Zambia, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 441)
  - Zimbabwe, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 442)
  - Anti- Apartheid Movement, 1982 (Box 51)
  - Conferences, 1977-1982 (Box 51)
  - Cultural Boycott of South Africa, 1981-1984 (Box 51)
  - Embargoes against South Africa, 1971-1984 (Box 51)
  - Halt all Racist Tours Movement, 1976 (Box 51)
  - International Commission of Enquiry, 1978-1979 (Box 51)
  - Irish Anti-Apartheid Movement, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 1226)
  - Kwik-Kopy printing, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 1227)
  - Mouvement Anti-Apartheid, 1971-1983 (Box 45, Folder 1228)
  - North American Regional Conference, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 1229)
  - Real Printing and Publishing Company (Spark), undated (Box 45, Folder 1230)
  - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 1231)
  - African National Congress, 1964-1979 (Box 52)
  - Arms Embargo Against South Africa, 1968 (Box 52)
  - Chetty, Shun, 1977-1981 (Box 52)
  - Committee for Solidarity with Peoples of Southern Africa, 1980 (Box 52)
  - Defense and Aid Fund, 1981 (Box 52)
  - Federation of South African Women, 1982 (Box 52)
  - Gleneagles Agreement, 1979 (Box 52)
  - Hlalukana, G., 1981 (Box 52)
  - Internal Papers of Special Committee Against Apartheid, 1968-1986 (Box 52)
  - International University Exchange Fund, 1972 (Box 52)
  - Korea, 1976-1978 (Box 52)
  - Oil Embargo Against South Africa, 1975-1983 (Box 52)
  - Pan Africanist Congress, 1967-1983 (Box 52)
  - South African Youth Revolutionary Council, 1982 (Box 52)
  - Thailand, 1979 (Box 52)
  - United Nations Educational and Training Program for Southern Africa (UNETPSA)
    - 1979-1984 (Box 52)
    - 1985 (Box 52)
  - UN Mission to Botswana, Lesotho and Swaziland, 1983 (Box 52)
  - Zaire, 1975 (Box 52)
  - Arms embargo against South Africa (Box 57)
  - British anti-apartheid (Box 57)
  - Nordic countries (Box 57)
  - Oil embargo against South Africa (four folders) (Box 57)
  - Sports boycott (Box 57)
- Anti-apartheid movements
  - Accuracy in Media, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 443)
  - Action Contre le Sida, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 444)
  - Africa Fund, 1972-1993 (Box 9, Folder 445-446)
  - Africa Groups in Sweden, 1979-1985 (Box 9, Folder 447)
  - African National Congress
    - 1963-1992 (Box 9, Folder 448 - 454)
    - Sechaba, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 455)
    - Women's Section, 1976-1984 (Box 9, Folder 456)
  - African Studies Association (New York), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 457)
  - Afrikagrupperna, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 458)
  - Afro-Asian People's Solidarity Organization, undated (Box 9, Folder 459)
  - Afro-Asian Solidarity Association of Ceylon, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 460)
  - Ahmadu Bello University Anti-Apartheid Movement: Nigeria, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 461)
  - Aktiekomitee Zuidelijk Afrika (AKZA), Belgium, 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 462)
  - American Committee on Africa (ACOA), 1960-1992 (Box 10, Folder 463-470)
  - American: South African People's Friendship Association, undated (Box 10, Folder 471)
  - Amnesty International, 1973-1992 (Box 10, Folder 472)
  - Anglicans in South Africa, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 473)
  - Anti-Apartheid Beweging Nederland (AABN), 1981-1993 (Box 10, Folder 474)
  - Anti-Apartheid: Bewegung (Austria), 1984 (Box 10, Folder 475)
  - Anti-Apartheid Bewegung: West Berlin, 1976-1987 (Box 10, Folder 476)
  - Anti-Apartheid Committee (Wellington), undated (Box 10, Folder 477)
  - Anti-Apartheid Group (Bermuda), 1983 (Box 10, Folder 478)
  - Anti-Apartheid Movement (Britain), 1965-1979 (Box 10, Folder 479)
  - Anti-Apartheid Movement (Britain), 1965-1991 (Box 11, Folder 480-487)
  - Anti-Apartheid Movement Women's Committee (AAMWC) (London), undated (Box 11, Folder 488)
  - Anti-Censorship Action Group (ACAG), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 489)
  - Anti-Imperialist Solidarity Committee for Africa, Asia and Latin America (Frankfurt), undated (Box 11, Folder 490)
  - Anti-Slavery Society for the Protection of Human Rights, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 491)
  - Art Against Apartheid, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 492)
  - Artists and Athletes Against Apartheid, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 493)
  - Association of National Olympic Committees of Africa (ANOCA, Paris), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 494)
  - Association of West European Parliamentarians for Action Against Apartheid (AWEPAA), 1984-1993 (Box 11, Folder 495)
  - Azania Committee (Netherlands), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 496)
  - Azania Solidarity Campaign (London), undated (Box 11, Folder 497)
  - Azanian People's Organization (AZAPO), 1982 (Box 11, Folder 498)
  - Bahamas Committee on Southern Africa (Bahamas), undated (Box 11, Folder 499)
  - Bishop Ambrose Reeves Trust (BART), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 500)
  - Black Consciousness Movement of Azania, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 501)
  - Black People's Convention (BPC), undated (Box 11, Folder 502)
  - Black Renaissance Convention, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 503)
  - Black Sash, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 504)
  - Black Student Alliance (BSA) (Los Angeles), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 505)
  - Boston Coalition for the Liberation of Southern Africa (BCLSA), 1979-1982 (Box 11, Folder 506)
  - Boycott Outspan Aktie (BAA), 1974-1978 (Box 11, Folder 507)
  - British Defense and Aid Fund for Southern Africa, 1970-1992 (Box 11, Folder 508)
  - Campaign Against Investment in South Africa (CAISA), undated (Box 12, Folder 509)
  - Campaign Against Racial Exploitation (CARE, Australia), 1983
  - Campaign to Oppose Bank Loans to South Africa, undated (Box 12, Folder 510)
  - Canadians Concerned About Southern Africa (Toronto), 1978-1985 (Box 12, Folder 511)
  - Capital District Coalition Against Apartheid and Racism, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 512)
  - Christian Concern for Southern Africa, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 513)
  - Coalition for Illinois' Divestment from South Africa, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 514)
  - Coalition to End Cultural Collaboration with South Africa (CECCSA), 1982 (Box 12, Folder 515)
  - Le Collectif de Recherche et d'Information sur l'Afrique Australe (CRIAA), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 516)
  - Comitato Nazionale Di Solidarieta Con I Popoli Dell Africa and Australe, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 517)
  - Comité Contre Le Colonialisme et L'Apartheid (CCCA) (Brussels), 1982 (Box 12, Folder 518)
  - Mouvement Contre le Racisme et pour l'Amitiéentre les Peuples (MRAP), 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 519)
  - Comite Latino American y Del Caribe Contra El Apartheid, undated (Box 12, Folder 520)
  - Committee for the Decade for Action to Combat Racism and Racial Discrimination (W. Germany), 1974-1981 (Box 12, Folder 521)
  - Committee on South African War Resistance (COSAWR), 1979-1988 (Box 12, Folder 522)
  - Committee to Oppose Bank Loans to South Africa, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 523)
  - Congress of South African Trade Unions (COSATU), 1986-1990 (Box 12, Folder 524)
  - Congress of South African Writers, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 525)
  - Connecticut Anti-Apartheid Committee, 1979-1983 (Box 12, Folder 526)
  - Council of Unions of South Africa (CUSA), 1983 (Box 12, Folder 527)
  - Cultural Foundation Against Apartheid (Paris), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 528)
  - Detainee Parents Support Committee (DPSC), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 529)
  - End Loans to Southern Africa (ELTSA), 1984-1991 (Box 12, Folder 530)
  - Episcopal Church People for a Free Southern Africa, 1982-1990 (Box 12, Folder 531)
  - Federation of South African Trade Unions (FOSATU), 1980 (Box 12, Folder 532)
  - Friends of Hunter and Hanekom's (Zimbabwe), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 533)
  - Ghana National committee Against Apartheid, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 534)
  - Halt All Racist Tours Movement Chart (New Zealand), 1976-1987 (Box 12, Folder 535)
  - Holland Committee on Southern Africa (Amsterdam), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 536)
  - Houstonians Against Apartheid, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 537)
  - Human Rights Commission, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 538)
  - Informationsstelle Sudliches Africa e. V. (ISSA, Bonn), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 539)
  - Inkatha, 1985-1992 (Box 12, Folder 540)
  - International Campaign Against Banking on Apartheid (ICABA), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 541)
  - International Committee Against Apartheid, Racism and Colonialism in Southern Africa (ICSA), 1977-1982 (Box 12, Folder 542-543)
  - International Co-ordinating Center Against Apartheid in Sport, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 544)
  - International Defense and Aid Fund (IDAF)
    - 1964-1989 (Box 12, Folder 545-546)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 547)
  - International Mobilization Against Apartheid and for Liberation of Southern Africa, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 548)
  - International Organization for the Elimination of All Forms of Racial Discrimination (EAFORD), undated (Box 13, Folder 549)
  - Irish Anti-Apartheid Movement (Dublin), 1965-1990 (Box 13, Folder 550-551)
  - Isolera Sydafrika Kommitten (ISAK, Sweden), 1980-1987 (Box 13, Folder 552)
  - Jamaica Anti-Apartheid Committee, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 553)
  - Japan Anti-Apartheid Committee (Tokyo), 1971-1987 (Box 13, Folder 554)
  - Komitee Zuidelijk Afrika (Amsterdam), 1974-1987 (Box 13, Folder 555-556)
  - Lawyers Against Apartheid, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 557)
  - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights Under Law, 1974-1993 (Box 13, Folder 558-561)
  - Madison Area Committee on Southern Africa, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 562)
  - Maritime Unions Against Apartheid (London), 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 563)
  - Mouvement Anti-Apartheid (Paris), 1979-1985 (Box 13, Folder 564)
  - Mouvement Anti-Apartheid De Suisse (Geneva), 1973-1982 (Box 13, Folder 565)
  - Conference in Terparlementraire Sur "La Santé- Base Du Développement en Afrique," Brazzaville, 1978-1983 (Box 13, Folder 566)
  - Natal Indian Congress (NIC), 1984 (Box 14, Folder 567)
  - National Anti-Apartheid Committee (Wellington), 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 568)
  - National Anti-Imperialist Movement in Solidarity with African Liberation (NAIMSAL), 1983 (Box 14, Folder 569)
  - National Committee Against Apartheid (NACAP, Lagos), 1963-1984 (Box 14, Folder 570)
  - National Committee of Health Organizations of South Africa, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 571)
  - National Olympic Committee of South Africa (NOCSA), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 572)
  - National Union of Seamen Campaign Against Oil and Arms to South Africa, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 573)
  - National Union of South African Students (NUSAS), 1964-1973 (Box 14, Folder 574)
  - New Haven Free South Africa Coalition, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 575)
  - New York Labor Committee Against Apartheid, 1984-1992 (Box 14, Folder 576)
  - New York- Southern Africa Solidarity Coalition, undated (Box 14, Folder 577)
  - New Zealand Anti-Apartheid Movement (HART), 1982 (Box 14, Folder 578)
  - New Zealand Defense and Aid Fund for Southern Africa (Wellington), 1977-1980 (Box 14, Folder 579)
  - Northeast Southern Africa Solidarity Network (NESAN), 1989 (Box 14, Folder 580)
  - Norwegian Council for Southern Africa, 1980-1985 (Box 14, Folder 581)
  - Oregonians for Responsible State Investments (ORSI), 1984 (Box 14, Folder 582)
  - Organization of African Unity (OAU), 1965-1993 (Box 14, Folder 583-588)
  - Oxfam (Canada), 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 589)
  - Pan Africanist Congress (PAC)
    - 1965-1980 (Box 14, Folder 590-593)
    - 1980-1993 (Box 15, Folder 594-595)
  - Parliamentarians Action for Removal of Apartheid (India), 1987 (Box 15, Folder 596)
  - Patrice Lumumba Coalition, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 597)
  - People of Southern African Freedom (PSAF), 1982 (Box 15, Folder 598)
  - People's Front for the Liberation of South Africa (Princeton), 1978 (Box 15, Folder 599)
  - Quebec Centre Against Apartheid and Racism in Sport, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 600)
  - Sisters Against South African Apartheid (SASAA), 1989 (Box 15, Folder 601)
  - Socialist International Southern Africa Committee (Amsterdam), 1985 (Box 15, Folder 602)
  - South Africa Committee (Denmark), 1982 (Box 15, Folder 603)
  - South Africa Freedom Fund, undated (Box 15, Folder 604)
  - South Africa Society, undated (Box 15, Folder 605)
  - South African Action National Committee (Denmark), 1979 (Box 15, Folder 606)
  - South African Colored Peoples' Congress, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 607)
  - South African Communist Party (SACP), 1989 (Box 15, Folder 608)
  - South African Congress of Trade Unions (SACTU), 1981-1990 (Box 15, Folder 609)
  - South African Council of Churches (SACC), 1984-1991 (Box 15, Folder 610)
  - South African Council on Sport (SACOS), 1977-1989 (Box 15, Folder 611)
  - South African Liberation Front (SALF), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 612)
  - South African Military Refugee Aid Fund (SAMRAF), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 613)
  - South African Non-Racial Olympic Committee (SANROC), 1970-1990 (Box 15, Folder 614)
  - South African Prep Council, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 615)
  - South African Students' Organization (SASO), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 616)
  - South African Students' Press Union (SASPU), 1982-1991 (Box 15, Folder 617)
  - South African Youth Revolutionary Council (SAYRCO), 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 618)
  - Southern Africa Anti-Mercenary Coalition, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 619)
  - Southern Africa Coalition, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 620)
  - Southern Africa Committee, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 621)
  - Southern Africa Defense and Aid Fund in Australia (SADAF), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 622)
  - Southern Africa Information Group (Canada), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 623)
  - Southern Africa Liberation Committee (SALC), 1978-1982 (Box 15, Folder 624)
  - Southern Africa Media Center, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 625)
  - Southern Africa Organizing Committee, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 626)
  - Southern Africa Relief Fund (SARF) (Nigeria), undated (Box 15, Folder 627)
  - Southern Africa Support Campaign (SASCA), 1983 (Box 15, Folder 628)
  - Southern Africa Support Project (SASP), undated (Box 15, Folder 629)
  - Southern Africa Task Force (Houston), 1983 (Box 15, Folder 630)
  - Southern African Affairs (Southscan), 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 631-632)
  - Southern African Information Programme (Geneva), 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 633)
  - Southern African News Agency (SANA), 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 634-635)
  - Soviet Afro-Asian Solidarity Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 636)
  - Stichting Anti-Apartheids Beweging Nederland (Amsterdam), 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 637)
  - Stichting West Europa Zuidelyk -Afrika (WEZA) Holland, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 638)
  - Students African Movement, undated (Box 15, Folder 639)
  - Support Committee for African Liberation Day (SCALD), 1982 (Box 15, Folder 640)
  - Supreme Council for Sport in Africa, 1979-1984 (Box 15, Folder 641)
  - Toronto Committee for the Liberation of Southern Africa (TCLSAC), 1979-1984 (Box 15, Folder 642)
  - Transafrica, 1977-1984 (Box 16, Folder 643-644)
  - Transvaal Rural Action Committee, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 645)
  - Union of Liberian Associations in the Americas, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 646)
  - United Democratic Front (UDF), 1983-1988 (Box 16, Folder 647)
  - U.S. Committee for Refugees, undated (Box 16, Folder 648)
  - U.S. Out of Southern Africa Network, undated (Box 16, Folder 649)
  - U.S. Peace Council, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 650)
  - Uniting Church South Africa Support Group (Melbourne), 1987 (Box 16, Folder 651)
  - Unity in Action, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 652)
  - Unity Movement of South Africa, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 653)
  - University Christian Movement, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 654)
  - Uruguayan Association Against Racism and Apartheid (Geneva), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 655)
  - Washington Office of Africa, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 656-659)
  - Welsh Anti-Apartheid Movement, 1980-1983 (Box 16, Folder 660)
  - World Campaign Against Military and Nuclear Collaboration with South Africa, 1981-1992 (Box 16, Folder 661)
  - Writers and Artists Against Apartheid, undated (Box 16, Folder 662)
  - Youth Solidarity on Southern Africa (YUSSA), 1983 (Box 16, Folder 663)
- Anti-Apartheid Conferences
  - African-American National Conference on Africa, Washington D.C., 1972 May 25-26 (Box 17, Folder 664)
  - African Conference of Parliamentarians on Population and Development, Harare, Zimbabwe, 1986 May (Box 17, Folder 665)
  - African International Conferences, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 666)
  - African National Congress, 75thAnniversary, 1987 January 8 (Box 17, Folder 667)
  - African Studies Association, Denver, 1971 November (Box 17, Folder 668)
  - All-Ireland Conference, Dublin, 1981 October 24 (Box 17, Folder 669)
  - Annual General Conference: Women's Brigade, Ulundi, 1984 October 20 (Box 17, Folder 670)
  - Anti-Apartheid Movement National Action Conference, "Southern Africa after Zimbabwe", 1980 May 31 (Box 17, Folder 671)
  - Anti-Apartheid Movement National Mobilizing Conference, London, 1981 March 21 (Box 17, Folder 672)
  - Anti-Apartheid Movement Trade Union Conference, "Isolate Apartheid," London, 1982 November 27 (Box 17, Folder 673)
  - Apartheid and Southern Africa: the West European Response, Amsterdam, 1985 September 12-14 (Box 17, Folder 674)
  - Arusha Conference of the Socialist International, 1984 September (Box 17, Folder 675)
  - Canadian Conference in Solidarity with the Liberation Struggle of the Peoples of Southern Africa, Ottawa, 1982 May 7-9 (Box 17, Folder 676)
  - Canberra Conference on Namibia, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 677)
  - Children, Apartheid, and Repression in Southern Africa, London, 1988 April 23 (Box 17, Folder 678)
  - Commission on the Program to Combat Racism (PCR), 1975 March 2-6 (Box 17, Folder 679)
  - Conference in Solidarity with the Liberation Struggles of the Peoples of Southern Africa, New York, 1981 October 9-11 (Box 17, Folder 680)
  - Séminaire Internationale sur L'Apartheid, Brasilia, 1988 June 27 (Box 17, Folder 681)
  - Conference of Arab Solidarity with the Struggle for Liberation in Southern Africa, Tunis, 1984 August 7-9 (Box 17, Folder 682)
  - Conference of Foreign Ministers of the Co-ordinating Bureau of Non Aligned Countries, New Delhi, 1977 April 7-11 (Box 17, Folder 683)
  - Conference of Maritime Trade Unions, London, 1985 October 30-31 (Box 17, Folder 684)
  - Conference of the Nordic Solidarity Organizations on Southern Africa, Oslo, 1978 January 7-8 (Box 17, Folder 685)
  - Conference of Western European Parliament Members on an Oil Embargo Against South Africa, Belgium, 1981 January 30-31 (Box 17, Folder 686)
  - Conference of Western European Parliament Members on Sanctions Against South Africa, The Hague, 1982 November 26-27 (Box 17, Folder 687)
  - Conference on Public Investment and South Africa, New York, 1981 June 12-13 (Box 17, Folder 688)
  - Conferences and Seminars Organized by the Special Committee Against Apartheid, 1977-1985 (Box 17, Folder 689)
  - Congressional Black Caucus 8thAnnual Weekend, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 690)
  - Congressional Southern Africa Conference, Washington D.C., 1976 September 9 (Box 17, Folder 691)
  - Cultural Voice of the Resistance: Dutch and South African Artists Against Apartheid, Amsterdam, 1983 December 12-18 (Box 17, Folder 692)
  - Donors' Conference on Emergency Assistance to Mozambique, New York, 1989 April 14 (Box 17, Folder 693)
  - Easter Conference, Lund, 1972 March (Box 17, Folder 694)
  - Eighteenth Strategy for Peace Conference, 1977 October 13-16 (Box 17, Folder 695)
  - Eighth Summit Conference of East and Central African States, Dar Es Salaam, 1972 September (Box 17, Folder 696)
  - Eighth European Sport Conference, Athens, 1987 September (Box 17, Folder 697)
  - Eleventh Congress of the International Association of Democratic Lawyers, Malta, 1980 November 13-17 (Box 17, Folder 698)
  - Evaluation Symposium on ICFTU (International Confederation of Free Trade Unions) Program of Action in Support of Independent Black Trade Union Movement in South Africa, Düsseldorf, 1984 January 19 (Box 17, Folder 699)
  - Fifth Summit Conference of East and Central African States, Lusaka, 1969 April 14-16 (Box 17, Folder 700)
  - "Fighting for Freedom," International Student Conference, London, 1987 June-August (Box 17, Folder 701)
  - Follow-up Conference on International Educational Assistance to Disadvantaged South Africans, New York, 1992 September 8-9 (Box 17, Folder 702)
  - Fourth All-Union Conference of Specialists in African Studies, Moscow, 1984 October 3-5 (Box 17, Folder 703)
  - Fourth International Conference Against Apartheid in Sport, Stockholm, 1990 September 4-6 (Box 17, Folder 704)
  - Fourth Regional Conference of African UNA's, Sierra Leone, 1985 February 4-8 (Box 17, Folder 705)
  - Front Line States Summit Meeting, Arusha, 1984 April 29 (Box 17, Folder 706)